<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>新卒募集 on Business Base Job</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/%E6%96%B0%E5%8D%92%E5%8B%9F%E9%9B%86/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 新卒募集 on Business Base Job</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright Business Base Job</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/%E6%96%B0%E5%8D%92%E5%8B%9F%E9%9B%86/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stripe</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad2/</guid>
      <description> 会社名 Stripe.inc
https://stripe.com/jp
求める人材  日本語がネイティブレベル。
 英語がビジネスレベル。
 顧客/クライアントへの営業経験が3年以上、トップセールスの実績がある。
 APIを理解でき、技術力の高い顧客と良好な関係を構築できる。
 企業の複雑な要件を理解し、カスタムソリューションを提案できる。
 不確定な要素に満ち、変化のペースが速い環境で業務を遂行する能力。
 スタートアップコミュニティや新しい技術のビジネスへの確かな情熱。
 会話および文章での優れたコミュニケーションスキル。
 テクノロジーへの高い関心。
 以下の経験があれば尚可
 成長ステージにあるインターネット/ソフトウェア企業での勤務経験。
 法人営業の経験。
 B2Bマーケティングの経験。
 決済サービス業界の経験。
  業務内容  企業の規模を問わず、有望な見込み顧客を選定し、新たな収益源として成長させます。
 経営幹部、オペレーションチーム、開発者との間に良好な関係を構築し、維持します。
 認知度を高めるための新しい販売戦略を策定、実施します
  Position Account Exective  こちらは【クローズ】の募集となります。
応募・詳細は以下のボタンからBusiness Base Huntに[Stripe]とメッセージ
応募はこちら   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>外資系フィンテック(企業名非公開)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad4/</guid>
      <description>会社名 外資系フィンテック  求める人材  At least 1 year of commercial sales experience  Professional skills: courteous, collaborative, creative, well spoken and polished in asking questions and sharing information -Competent in multi-tasking  Able to connect business needs to high impact solutions -Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree, preferably in Business Administration, Marketing or Communications
  業務経験  Make outbound calls to prospects who have expressed interest in learning more about DocuSign</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>米系フィンテック(企業名非公開)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad3/</guid>
      <description>会社名 非公開(コンタクト後公開)  求める人材  Enjoy writing, and do so quickly and clearly (you need to be fluent and highly proficient in Japanese and English).
 Enjoy talking about technical concepts, have great analytical skills, and would be comfortable explaining how our works to a range of audiences.
 Can empathize with users and quickly grasp the issues they’re facing.
 Enjoy the puzzle of solving open-ended problems.
 Love constantly learning about a changing technical product, even when it’s a little out of your depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>外資系ファンド(企業名非公開)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad1/</guid>
      <description> 会社名 米系投資ファンド　foreign investment fund  求める人材  新卒(ファイナンス専攻が好ましい)、または24歳以下でビジネス英語のできる者 金融業界に興味のある者 日本語が話せる  Position Junior position  Salary 基本給 ~　600万円 + ボーナス  Start Data 2018年4月~  こちらは【クローズ】の募集となります。
応募・詳細は以下のボタンからBusiness Base Huntに[外資系ファンド]とメッセージ。
応募はこちら   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>