<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>英語 on Business Base Job</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AA%9E/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 英語 on Business Base Job</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright Business Base Job</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AA%9E/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lincoln International</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/intern6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/intern6/</guid>
      <description> 会社名 リンカーンインターナショナル  求める人材 非公開  Position ポジション状況によって変動  Salary 非公開  選考方法 1次 CV + Coverletter → 2次 面接  こちらは【オープン】の募集となります。
応募・詳細は以下のボタンから
応募はこちら  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stripe</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad2/</guid>
      <description> 会社名 Stripe.inc
https://stripe.com/jp
求める人材  日本語がネイティブレベル。
 英語がビジネスレベル。
 顧客/クライアントへの営業経験が3年以上、トップセールスの実績がある。
 APIを理解でき、技術力の高い顧客と良好な関係を構築できる。
 企業の複雑な要件を理解し、カスタムソリューションを提案できる。
 不確定な要素に満ち、変化のペースが速い環境で業務を遂行する能力。
 スタートアップコミュニティや新しい技術のビジネスへの確かな情熱。
 会話および文章での優れたコミュニケーションスキル。
 テクノロジーへの高い関心。
 以下の経験があれば尚可
 成長ステージにあるインターネット/ソフトウェア企業での勤務経験。
 法人営業の経験。
 B2Bマーケティングの経験。
 決済サービス業界の経験。
  業務内容  企業の規模を問わず、有望な見込み顧客を選定し、新たな収益源として成長させます。
 経営幹部、オペレーションチーム、開発者との間に良好な関係を構築し、維持します。
 認知度を高めるための新しい販売戦略を策定、実施します
  Position Account Exective  こちらは【クローズ】の募集となります。
応募・詳細は以下のボタンからBusiness Base Huntに[Stripe]とメッセージ
応募はこちら   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>アバディーン投信投資顧問株式会社</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/intern5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/intern5/</guid>
      <description>会社名 アバディーン投信投資顧問株式会社  業務内容  Learn the equity investment process in Aberdeen way
 Contribute to investment decisions as part of the team
 Meet with Management of companies large and small
 Listen first-hand to the views of industry experts
 Delve deep into industry fundamentals and analyse companies across various sectors
  Position Fund Manager Intern  Salary 非公開  求める人材  新卒、または単位の取得が終了した方
 向上心があり、他者を導ける者
 難しいこともシンプルにわかりやすく話せるコミュニケーション能力と社交性</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ソシエテ・ジェネラル</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/intern7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/intern7/</guid>
      <description>会社名 ソシエテ・ジェネラル  業務内容  Structuring of new products (design of the product, its commercial pitch and legal documentation, as well as engineering of its internal management processes, on all types of underlyings – equities, rates, FX, credit, alternative investment)
 Ongoing maintenance of existing clients and products (client queries, performance analysis, secondary market requests)
 Management of exceptional events affecting products after their launch
 Pricing
  Position Corporate and Investment Banking Intern  Salary 非公開  求める人材  Quantitative background</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>外資系デザイン会社(非公開)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/intern3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/intern3/</guid>
      <description>会社名 外資系デザイン会社  業務内容  Work with the on-site Social Media Manager to create and implement campaigns. Develop content calendars on a weekly and monthly basis for company brands. Monitor analytics with social media team to identify viable ideas. Create engaging blog and social media content. Assist in the general distribution of press releases and media alerts. Provide support to our marketing team at live and online events.  Position Social Media Interns  求められるスキル  Excellent oral and written communication skills (English) Good knowledge of Social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>外資系フィンテック(企業名非公開)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad4/</guid>
      <description>会社名 外資系フィンテック  求める人材  At least 1 year of commercial sales experience  Professional skills: courteous, collaborative, creative, well spoken and polished in asking questions and sharing information -Competent in multi-tasking  Able to connect business needs to high impact solutions -Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree, preferably in Business Administration, Marketing or Communications
  業務経験  Make outbound calls to prospects who have expressed interest in learning more about DocuSign</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>株式会社BMW</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/intern4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/intern4/</guid>
      <description>会社名 BMW / ビーエムダブリュー  求める人材  Currently doing a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree
 Japanese (Business-Native Level), English (Business Level), German (Good to have)
 Microsoft Office (PowerPoint, Excel and Outlook)
 Ability to work 5 days a week for 6 months
 Valid Visa that allows interning for 37.5h a week (We will provide supporting documents upon request for your visa application)
  Position マーケティング/ファイナンス/エンジニア(インターン)  Salary 月15万円  こちらは【オープン】ポジションです。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>米系フィンテック(企業名非公開)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/newgrad3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/newgrad3/</guid>
      <description>会社名 非公開(コンタクト後公開)  求める人材  Enjoy writing, and do so quickly and clearly (you need to be fluent and highly proficient in Japanese and English).
 Enjoy talking about technical concepts, have great analytical skills, and would be comfortable explaining how our works to a range of audiences.
 Can empathize with users and quickly grasp the issues they’re facing.
 Enjoy the puzzle of solving open-ended problems.
 Love constantly learning about a changing technical product, even when it’s a little out of your depth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>